Privacy Policy for Territorial.io Last Updated: March 19, 2024 Introduction: Welcome to Territorial.io. Developed and operated by David Tschacher, this Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, and safeguard the information you provide to us. 1. Information Collection: Stored on the User's Device and Transmitted to Our Servers: - User Settings: This includes preferred resolution and user interface size. - Username: This pertains to the user's in-game identity. - Password: Specifically for the user's one-vs-one account. - Preferred Game Assets: User's choice of colors and flags. - Preferred Color: This is for personalizing the user experience. - Game Data: Necessary information for the multiplayer experience, such as which country the user attacks. - IP Addresses: These are logged but do not include identifying information like real names, addresses, or phone numbers. - Crash Logs: To assist in improving the game's stability. - Replay Files: Replay files of games in multiplayer can be stored and distributed by participating players. Collected by third parties: - Third parties may use the Android advertising ID and other identifiers. - Third parties may use the user's name, address, email address, or telephone number. 2. Data Use: - Gameplay Enhancement: The data is essential for facilitating the multiplayer experience. - Data Analysis: For insights such as determining popular maps. - Public Lists: We publish lists featuring one-vs-one players detailing usernames, played games, and ELO numbers. Clans and their relevant statistics are also made public. - Crash Analysis: To identify issues and improve gameplay experience. - Ad Targeting and Personalization: We use data to display personalized advertisements. 3. Data Sharing: - Discord: Usernames and certain gameplay statistics may be shared on Discord, including results from one-vs-one matches. - Statistical Data: We may release anonymous, aggregated game data for public view. - AdMob: Our app uses AdMob for advertisements. Please review https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites to understand their data practices, including their collection of Android advertising ID and other identifiers. - AdinPlay: Our website uses AdinPlay for advertisements. This company may use information about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp 4. Data Protection: - Secure Transmission: All data sent to our servers is transmitted over secure websocket connections. - Third-party Advertisers: We have no control over information collected by third parties like AdMob. We encourage you to review their privacy policy. 5. User Rights: - Data Deletion: In special circumstances, users may request the removal of their data from our servers. - Ad Consent: Information regarding a user's choice of ad consent may be stored on their device. 6. Changes to Privacy Policy: We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any given time. Any changes made will be effective immediately upon updating the policy. Regularly reviewing this policy is the best way to stay informed about our data practices. 7. Contact: For any queries or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please reach out to: David Tschacher Email: davidtschacher@gmail.com By using Territorial.io, you consent to this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with any terms listed here, please refrain from using our services.
